although inkscape is meant for working
尽管Inkscape是为工作而设计的
with vector graphics
使用矢量图形
it does have some features and tools
它确实有一些功能和工具
that allow you to make common edits to
允许您对以下内容进行常见编辑
photographs and other types of
照片和其他类型的
rasterized images
栅格化图像
and even though you'd be better off
即使你会过得更好
using proper photo editing software for
使用适当的照片编辑软件
this sort of thing
这类事情
you may find yourself working in a
你可能会发现自己在一个
vector environment once in a while
向量环境偶尔出现
and needing to just make a quick edit to
并且只需快速编辑即可
an image
一个形象
in these instances launching yet another
在这些情况下，又推出了另一个
application can be an inconvenience
申请可能会带来不便
this is where inkscape's photo editing
这就是Inkscape的照片编辑
ability comes in handy
能力派上用场
and in this video i'll be going over 8
在这段视频中，我将超过8
different ways in which you can edit
您可以使用不同的方式进行编辑
photos
照片
in inkscape
在Inkscape
[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynick.com and in
我是来自logosbynick.com的尼克
this video i'll be going over some of
这段视频我将回顾一些
the ways in which you can edit photos in
在中编辑照片的方式
inkscape
墨迹
but before we get started if you'd like
但在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
to learn everything that there is to
去学习所有需要学习的东西
know about inkscape be sure to check out
了解Inkscape，一定要查看
my inkscape master class
我的Inkscape大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape
在Inkscape
and i explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works i'll have a link in the
它是如何工作的，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out
看看这个
the first way in which you can edit a
编辑的第一种方法
photo in inkscape is by cropping it
Inkscape中的照片是通过裁剪的
to crop your photo all you have to do is
要裁剪你的照片，你需要做的就是
create a rectangle going over the
在上面创建一个矩形
portion of the photo you'd like to crop
您要裁剪的照片部分
and then create a clipping mask from it
然后用它创建一个剪贴蒙版
from there you can just resize your
从那里，您只需调整您的
document based on the cropped image by
基于裁剪的图像的文档
pressing ctrl
按Ctrl键
shift and r and then from there you can
Shift和r，然后从那里您可以
export your work as a png file
将您的工作导出为PNG文件
i'll have a tutorial linked in the
我会有一个教程链接在
description of the video if you need
视频描述(如果需要)
more details
更多细节
not only can clipping pads be used to
剪贴板不仅可以用来
crop photos in inkscape
在Inkscape中裁剪照片
but they can also be used to extract
但它们也可以用来提取
subjects from the photo
照片中的主题
this allows you to do all kinds of
这允许您执行所有类型的
unique things like create a photo
独特的东西，比如创建一张照片
pop-out effect or
弹出效果或
remove a background from an image these
从这些图像中删除背景
extractions can be made by simply
提取可以通过简单的
grabbing the bezier pen
抓起贝塞尔钢笔
and manually drawing a path around the
并手动绘制一条绕
subject you'd like to extract
您要提取的主题
then from there you can create a
然后您可以从那里创建一个
clipping path from it by selecting both
通过同时选择这两个选项来从其中裁剪路径
objects
对象
and navigating to object clip set
并导航到对象剪贴集
another way that you can edit photos in
在中编辑照片的另一种方式
inkscape is by adjusting their opacity
Inkscape是通过调整它们的不透明度
and inkscape allows you to change
Inkscape允许您更改
opacity values in a variety of different
各种不同类型的不透明度值
ways
途径
you can change the overall opacity of an
您可以更改
image by selecting it and opening the
图像，方法是将其选中并打开
fill and stroke menu
填充和描边菜单
from there grab the opacity slider and
从那里抓起不透明度滑块，然后
adjust it to your liking
根据你的喜好调整它
you can also give a photo partial
你也可以给一张照片部分
transparency or a transparency gradient
透明度或透明度渐变
by using layer masks this makes it so
通过使用层蒙版，可以做到这一点
that one side of an image is visible
图像的一侧是可见的
but gradually tapers off to transparency
但逐渐向透明度靠拢
this can be really useful when designing
这在设计时非常有用
things like headers and posters where
像标题和海报这样的东西
you need to incorporate imagery with
您需要将图像与
text in other vector elements
其他向量元素中的文本
layer masking is somewhat of an advanced
层遮罩在某种程度上是一种高级
topic but the gist of it is that you
主题，但它的主旨是你
create an object with the black and
创建一个带有黑色和
white gradient
白色渐变
and then apply it over your image as a
然后将其应用于您的图像作为
mask the black areas create a
遮罩黑色区域创建一个
transparent area in the photo whereas
照片中的透明区域，而
the white areas remain opaque
白色区域仍然是不透明的
i'll have a tutorial for this linked in
我会有一个关于这个的教程链接在
the description of the video if you want
视频的描述(如果需要
a more in-depth explanation
更深入的解释
inkscape also allows you to make some
Inkscape还允许您制作一些
common color adjustments to your photos
对照片进行常见的色彩调整
for example you can invert the colors of
例如，您可以反转
an image by selecting it and navigating
通过选择图像并导航该图像
to filters
到筛选器
colors invert you can also make your
颜色反转还可以使您的
image black and white
图像黑白
or grayscale by navigating to filters
或通过导航到滤镜进行灰度调整
color
颜色
grayscale and from there you can adjust
灰度，您可以从那里进行调整
the rgb values to your liking
根据您的喜好选择RGB值
in fact the filters menu has lots of
事实上，过滤器菜单有很多
interesting and unique effects that can
有趣而独特的效果，可以
be applied to your images
应用于您的图像
so be sure to browse through there and
所以一定要浏览一下那里和
experiment for yourself
为自己做实验
speaking of color adjustments inkscape
谈到颜色调整Inkscape
also allows you to make some more
还可以让你做更多
advanced color corrections like color
高级颜色校正，如颜色
channels and
渠道和
levels and hsb values all you have to do
级别和hsb值，您需要做的就是
to access these settings is navigate to
要访问这些设置，请导航到
extensions
扩展部分
and raster and from there you will have
和栅格，从那里你将拥有
a wide array of raster effects that you
广泛的栅格效果，您可以
can use to edit your photos in inkscape
可以使用在Inkscape中编辑您的照片
in a past tutorial i used these effects
在过去的教程中，我使用了这些效果
to create a carved wood effect
创建雕刻的木头效果
from an image of a piece of wood
从一块木头的图像
another common edit you may like to
您可能会喜欢的另一个常见编辑
apply to your photos once in a while is
偶尔适用于你的照片是
to apply a blur or maybe sharpen your
应用模糊或可能锐化您的
image
图像
to apply a blur open the fill and stroke
要应用模糊，请打开填充和笔触
menu by pressing ctrl
通过按Ctrl键选择菜单
shift and the letter a on your keyboard
Shift键和键盘上的字母a
and from there you can use the blur
从那里你可以使用模糊
slider to apply a gaussian blur to your
滑块将高斯模糊应用到您的
liking
喜欢
to sharpen your image simply navigate to
要锐化图像，只需导航到
filters
过滤器
image effects and select sharpen
图像效果并选择锐化
unfortunately
不幸的是
there's no way to adjust the threshold
没有办法调整门槛
of the filter but this can still be a
但这仍然可以是一个
handy trick
得心应手的把戏
for a quick touch-up
进行快速润色
as we went over earlier you can use the
正如我们前面所说的，您可以使用
bezier pen to manually draw
手动绘制的贝塞尔钢笔
shapes over subjects to extract them
对对象进行形状调整以提取它们
from their background
从他们的背景来看
if the background you'd like to remove
如果要删除的背景
is white though then you won't need to
是白色的，那么你就不需要
go through all of that trouble
经历了所有这些麻烦
you can simply use the trace bitmap
您可以简单地使用跟踪位图
feature to generate a vector silhouette
用于生成矢量轮廓的功能
of your subject then apply it as a
然后将其应用为
clipping path
剪裁路径
it should be noted that this method is
需要注意的是，这种方法是
far from perfect there are instances
一点也不完美，有这样的例子
where the auto trace feature won't be
自动跟踪功能将不会在
able to make an accurate distinction
能够做出准确的区分
between the foreground and the
在前台和
background
背景
but when it does work it can save you an
但当它起作用时，它可以为您节省
incredible amount of time
难以置信的时间
the final method that you can deploy for
您可以部署的最后一种方法
editing photos in inkscape
在Inkscape中编辑照片
is using blend modes this is somewhat of
正在使用混合模式这在某种程度上
a hidden feature in inkscape that not a
水墨景观中隐藏的特征，而不是
lot of users know about
很多用户都知道
to access it open your layers menu by
要访问它，通过以下方式打开您的层菜单
pressing ctrl
按ctrl
shift and l on your keyboard from there
从那里开始在键盘上输入ove和l
you can add a new layer on top of your
您可以在您的顶部添加新层
image layer
图像层
and any of the contents placed on that
以及上面放置的任何内容
layer can be blended into the image
层可以混合到图像中
beneath it
它下面
using the blend mode drop down near the
使用混合模式在
bottom of the menu
菜单底部
as you could imagine we've only begun to
正如你可以想象的那样，我们才刚刚开始
scratch the surface of all the different
触及所有不同的表面
ways that you can edit photos in
编辑照片的方式
inkscape
Inkscape
although these features may not be as
尽管这些功能可能不像
robust or intuitive as a raster image
作为格栅图像稳健或直观
editor like
编辑喜欢
they can still come in handy if you just
如果你只是，它们仍然可以派上用场
need a quick and basic edit
需要快速且基本的编辑
and you don't feel like launching
你不想发射
another application let me know in the
另一个应用程序让我知道
comments if there's any ways that you
如果您有任何方法，请评论
like to edit photos in inkscape that i
喜欢在水墨景观中编辑照片
may not have gone over in this video
在这个视频中可能没有过去
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]